Now that the Jupyter Notebook is up and running,
Jupyter Notebookが起動したので
you can use it to classify traffic signs.
これを使用して交通標識を分類できます
First, reset the kernel and clear the output to ensure you have a fresh start.
まず カーネルをリセットして 出力をクリアし 初めからやり直せるようにします
Next, clear the cell that loads
次に MNISTデータをロードするセルを
the MNIST data and replace it with code to load the traffic sign data.
クリアして 交通標識データをロードするコードで置き換えます
You can find that code in the notebook for the traffic sign classifier project.
ノートブックに交通標識クラシファイプロジェクトのコードが入りました
You should also delete the code that adds the images since
画像を追加するコードを削除することもできます
the traffic sign images are already 32 by 32 pixels.
交通標識画像はすでに32x32ピクセルだからです
One problem to solve though is that
完全に解決すべき問題の1つは
the traffic sign data does not come with a validation set.
交通標識データには評価セットが付いていないことです
You can use the train test split function in
Sklearnライブラリのトレーニングテスト分割関数を使用して
You can allocate as much of the training set as you want,
必要な数だけトレーニングセットをバリデーションセットとして割り当てることができますが、
20 percent is a good rule of thumb.
経験則的では２０％が良いでしょう
Now, you can visualize an image from the dataset.
これでデータセットの画像を視覚化できます
But remember, that the traffic sign images are in
しかし 交通標識画像はカラーであり
color not gray scale like the MNIST images.
MNIST画像のようなグレースケールではありません
It's worth looking in the GitHub Repo to compare the image label to
GitHubリポジトリの画像ラベルとCSVファイルを比較して
the CSV file that matches numerical labels to text descriptions.
数値ラベルとテキスト記述を照合するとよいでしょう
In this case, the numeric label is 35,
この場合 数値ラベルは35であり
which corresponds to a head only which looks correct.
対応するのはhead onlyであり 正しいようです
You can proceed to pre-process the data and set up TensorFlow just as we did for MNIST.
データを前処理して MNISTと同様にTensorFlowをセットアップできます
You'll have to make a few changes to the LeNet architecture though.
ただし LeNetアーキテクチャーにいくつかの変更を加える必要があります
First, remember that the traffic sign images or in color not gray scale,
まず 交通標識画像はカラーでありグレースケールではないので
so the input depth should be three to match the three RGB color channels.
入力深さはRGBカラーチャンネルに合わせて3でなければなりません
The new input depth won't affect the rest of the network architecture.
新しい入力深さは残りのネットワークアーキテクチャーに影響を与えません
Also at the output layer the traffic sign classifier has 43 classes,
また出力層では交通標識クラシファイは43クラスあり
whereas MNIST only had 10 so you'll have to change that.
一方 MNISTには10しかないので 変更する必要があります
When you set up the TensorFlow placeholders,
TensorFlowプレースホルダーをセットアップするときには
you'll have to update the input and output
入力および出力形状を再び更新して
shapes again to match the shapes of the new dataset.
新しいデータセットの形状に合わせなければなりません
Training the network should be the same as well so let's run it and see how it does.
ネットワークのトレーニングは同じなので 実行してみましょう
Ninety six percent validation accuracy that's pretty good for the first shot.
96％の検証精度は第一弾としてはかなり良いです
Remember don't run the test set until you're done
モデルの調整が完了し トレーニングを中止して
tuning the model and you're ready to stop training and submit the project.
プロジェクトを送信する準備ができるまで テストセットを実行しないでください